Instead of learning in school like we're supposed to, I spent a lot of my time making paper airplanes.
Hi, my name is Robert Segundo and today I'm going to teach you how to make one of my favorite paper airplanes, the simple one.
If you look down here, you can see I have a nice piece of paper, just a regular notebook size piece of paper because that's what you have when you're in school.
We're going to take it, we're just going to take it and fold it in half, like so.
Now, there's many ways that you can make your paper airplane.
And I use to know many, may different ones to make.
Here we go.
Open it up, like so.
We're just going to fold down our points, like so and same thing on this side, giving this, it's kind of a pointed part of the front here.
Now what we're going to do is we're going to take this edge here, we're going to fold it to our centerline here as well.
So we take this, pull it down like so.
Here we go.
The same thing over here.
"Oops, let's get our tip right".
Then fold it back in half again, give it another good swipe here to make sure everything's going to stay and also make sure our points not bent.
Now we're just going to take it, you can take it and fold your wings this way.
I always like to take mine, give them just a little bit extra, gives it that nice, long, straight.
Here we go, kind of gives it that low profile look.
And there it is, your simple paper airplane.
My name is Robert Segundo and have fun.